我们回来了
We're back!
发生了件超搞笑的事
Funniest thing --
斯黛拉散步时爱上了一只狗狗
Stella fell in love with this dog on our walk,
她就这么含情脉脉地凝望着
just stared at it lovingly.
结果发现那是她在轮毂罩映出的像
Turned out to be her reflection in a hubcap.
搞得人哭笑不得
Can you blame her?
话说我历史考试拿了个A
I got an "A" on my history exam, by the way.
你当真要和狗狗争宠吗
Really, you're competing with the dog?
别理他 乖孩子
Don't let it bother you, girl.
杰 咱们得谈谈
Jay, we need to talk.
我今天到过敏症医生那去了
I went to an allergist today,
他认为乔身上的疹子是过敏引起的
and he thinks that Joe's rash is an allergy.
真厉害 过敏症医生发现过敏症状了
What a surprise -- an allergist found an allergy.
他认为乔可能对斯黛拉过敏
He thinks he might be allergic to Stella.
什么
What?
这只狗带来的唯一反应就是引人发笑
The only reaction this dog gives people is the giggles.
当她想舔自己脸的时候...
I mean, when she tried to lick her own face...
在我们村 如果一只山羊有那么笨
In my village, if a goat acted that dumb,
我们都不会吃它
we wouldn't even eat it.
过敏这事不是开玩笑
This allergy thing is very serious.
我们得把他俩分开一星期
We need to separate them for a week
看看疹子会不会消褪
to see if the rash goes away.
那么久看不到乔我可能会受不了
I don't know if I can go that long without seeing Joe.
不是乔要走 是狗要走
Not joe! The dog!
我已经给米奇和卡梅隆打过电话了
I already called Mitch and Cameron.
他们可以照顾她
They're gonna take her.
走一星期吗
For a week?!
她会心灵受伤 她可是很敏感的
She'll be traumatized! She's very sensitive!
她是只会在车道上蹭屁股的狗
She scrapes her butt on the driveway.
你怎么就这么不待见她
Why don't you like her?
她跟你什么仇什么怨
She's never done anything to you.
你自己瞧 我的面霜
Ay, look! My face cream!
你知道这东西多少钱吗
Do you know how much this costs?
不知道 多少钱啊
No. How much?
别转移话题
Don't change the subject!
这狗现在就得走
The dog goes now!
这么一提我才发现
You know, now that I think about it,
我可能也对斯黛拉过敏
I could be allergic to Stella.
自从她来了我就有点呼吸困难[古板]
I've been a little stuffy since we got her.
斯黛拉没来前你就很古板
You were stuffy long before Stella.
你不记得那次你在芝士店批评服务员
Do you not remember scolding that waiter at Chuck E. Cheese
只是因为他是从右边上餐吗
for serving you from the right?
维多利亚式
Victorian.
现代
Modern.
纯木工
Craftsman.
西班牙式
Spanish.
欧洲的 哥特式
European...Gothic?
安迪 这是《冰雪奇缘》里的城堡
Andy, it's the castle from "Frozen".
很抱歉 你没准备好
I'm sorry, but you're not ready.
什么
What?
听到"你准备好了"这个消息
To hear that you're ready!
恭喜你 助理
Congratulations, assistant!
我要引领你到另一个境界
I'm moving you up to the next level.
苍天啊
Holy cow.
刚才可把人紧张坏了
That was an emotional thrill ride.
这个周日
This Sunday,
你要负责销售林登那里的科德角式房
you are manning the open house of the Cope Cod on Linden.
这意味着你负责在街边
That means you're gonna be sticking
安放好售房标志和气球
the sign and the balloons on the corner,
你负责把所有灯打开
you're gonna be turning on all the lights,
你负责烤好布朗尼蛋糕
you're gonna be baking all the brownies.
我会让您为我骄傲的 先生
I will make you proud, sir.
你还要负责干什么
What else are you gonna do?
我要确保客人登记好信息
I will make sure people sign in.
还有什么
What else?
我给客人展示主卧的时候
When I show someone the master bedroom,
我会说 "这是奇迹发生的地方"
I'll say, "This is where the magic happens."
-保准能卖掉 -太好了
- I'm sold! - Yes!
小伙伴 我等下要去商场
Hey, buddy. I got to hit the mall a little later.
你想不想到按摩椅上去享受下
You wanna grab a couple of chair massages
直到他们赶我们走
till they kick us out?
不了 我要跟几个朋友出去玩
Nah. I'm gonna go hang out with some of my friends.
好吧
Okay.
玩得开心
Have fun.
现在的青少年啊
Teenagers, huh?
是啊 越来越不想和我一起
Yeah, it's been happening more and more,
但这正常
but it's natural.
这个年龄的小孩需要空间
Kids that age want distance.
昨天他还紧紧抓着你的手
One day, they're holding your hand so tight it hurts.
第二天他们就把你想吃的苹果给吃了
The next day, they're eating the apple you kind of wanted.
我可不会
Not me.
我从来不会拒绝和我爸一起玩
I never turned down an offer to hang with my dad.
他很走运 我开始叛逆之前他就去世了
Luckily for him, he died before my rebellious teenage years.
肯定是外公和斯黛拉
That must be grandpa with Stella.
记住 莉莉 她只会在这呆一周
Remember, Lily, she's only gonna be here for a week,
她不会变成我们今后的宠物
She's not gonna be our permanent pet.
别跟我说 告诉拉里
Don't tell me, tell Larry.
他一整天都嫉妒得要死
He's been acting jealous all day.
你想太多了
You're being crazy!
老爸你好
Hey, Dad.
杰 你好 瞧瞧我们的小稀客
Hey, Jay.There's our precious little houseguest.
好了 听清楚
Okay, guys, listen up.
她每天要散三次步
She gets three walks a day.
别让她上床 我们在训练这个
Keep her off the bed. We're training her.
吃鸡不能带骨头 如果她开始喘气
No chicken bones. If she starts to wheeze --
记不记得那次你送我去夏令营
Remember when you dropped me off at summer camp?
你车都没停稳就把我撂了下来
You barely slowed down the car.
你又没有会让你难以呼吸的病症
You never had a condition that made it difficult to breathe.
我当时是运动夏令营里没出柜的同性恋
I was a closeted gay kid at sports camp.
我一整周都迷迷糊糊的
I spent the week in mid-faint.
莉莉 别忘了多揉揉斯黛拉的小肚肚
Lily, don't forget to give Stella lots of belly rubs.
爷爷 这件事
Grandpa, this is coming
对我和拉里而言来的不是时候
at a really bad time for me and Larry.
好了 你别担心
Okay, well, now, don't you worry
莉莉现在还不喜欢你这件事
about wily not woving you yet.
你怎么这么可爱呢
Aw, who's the little weeble wobble?
-我看不下去了 -老爸再见
- I can't watch this. Okay. - Bye, Dad.
我也不知道 平常要是没事
Oh, I don't know. I guess in my free time,
我喜欢关注有关再生能源的
I like to keep up with the latest discoveries
最新研究
in renewable energy.
记住 再过几个月
Just think, a few more months
你就再也不用经历这事了
and you'll never have to deal with this again.
我不介意参加大学面试
You know, I don't mind college interviews.
我其实挺喜欢和他们讨论一些
I actually like discussing the things that they --
我刚在跟镜子说话
I was talking to the mirror.
我知道你想上的大学只需要你
I know all you had to do to get in your college
关注他们的Facebook就够了
was like their Facebook page,
但这可是普林斯顿大学
But this is Princeton.
我要向他们展现我缜密的思维
I have to show them that I'm a serious thinker,
你就不能支持我一下吗
and you could be a bit more supportive.
好吧 很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
你的衣服很棒
Your outfit's perfect.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果你是要申请伐木学校的话
If you're applying to lumberjack school.
而且主修的是在死后被自己的猫吃掉
And majoring in having your cats eat you when you die.
早上好啊
Well, hello.
第一天感觉如何 回到衣柜...
How was your first day back in the closet...
行业工作
business?
你在说什么 我根本就没在这工作过
That doesn't make any sense. I've never worked here before.
那只是个基佬笑话 米奇尔
It's just a gay joke, Mitchell.
别想多了
Don't overthink it.
你还适应吗
You settling in?
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
我是说 我穿着牛仔裤 在上班
I mean, you know, I'm in jeans and I'm at work --
感觉像是个技工
I feel like a mechanic.
我很期待
I am looking forward
来给我爸做几天自由法律工作
to doing a few days of freelance legal work for my dad
因为在我上班的公司
because, uh, where I work,
我有个不太公平的名声
I've gotten the unfair reputation
"办公室里的唠叨鬼" 这...
of being the office nag, which is...
那只是因为我跟一群懒汉一起工作
See, it's only because I work with a bunch of slobs.
我每天必须告诉那些人50次
I mean, I must tell these people 50 times a day --
擦干净微波炉 清洗咖啡壶
"Wipe down the microwave," "Clean the coffee pot,"
这是谁的发霉的午餐肉啊 凯文
"Whose moldy lunch meat is this, Kevin?"
这回你请假的时候
So, did they put up much of a fight
他们有没有力争一番啊
when you asked for that time off, or...?
这里真好 很随意
Yeah, it's so nice and casual here.
我等不及想展示我潇洒的一面了
I can't wait to get my chill on.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
什么啊 我就是这样
What? This is me.
才不是
No, it's not.
接下来的几天我就是这样
For the next few days it is.
我离开这里时
When I leave here,
男人会想成为我 女人会想跟我购物
men will want to be me, women will want to shop with me.
你想过
Have you ever thought of
在你的常规工作那边更友好一些吗
trying to be nicer at your regular job? Mm.
我也是慢慢学着
I mean, I've had to learn
如何在做朋友和做经理之间保持平衡
how to balance being a friend and a manager.
你可以称之为做"朋理"
You could call it being a "Franager."
但我没必要 对吧
But I don't have to, right?
有必要
Yes, you do.
我是你老板 你得听我的一切吩咐
I am your boss. You have to do everything I say.
好吧 露西来了
Okay, all right, here comes Lucy.
她是新来的 爸爸想让我跟她谈谈
She's new, and dad wants me to talk to her
她的穿衣打扮
about the way she dresses.
他说那令人分心
He says it's distracting.
学着点 露西就要被"朋理"了
Watch and learn. Lucy's about to get franaged.
真棒 还能当动词用呐
Oh, good, it's a verb, too.
好啊 露西
Hey, Luce.
好啊 邓菲女士
Oh, hi, Ms. Dunphy.
不 拜托 我爸爸才是邓菲女士
Oh, no, come on. Please, my dad is Ms. Dunphy.
我只是克莱尔
I'm just Claire.
如果你想买一些上班时穿的衣服
So, listen, if you were looking for some clothes for work,
诺德斯特姆在搞大减价呢
Nordstrom's having a fabulous sale.
我在那里选了这件得体的小码衣服
I picked up this appropriate little number there.
我会去看看的
Well, I'll have to check that out.
-真棒 -谢谢
- Great. - Thanks.
看到我刚做的事了吗
See what I just did there?
我得去工作了
I got to get back to work.
你一会儿想一起吃午餐吗
Do you want to have lunch later?
你不跟大伙儿去面食工厂吗
Aren't you going to the Pasta Factory with the gang?
有谁要过生日吗
Oh, is it somebody's birthday?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
他们每周一都去那里
Uh, something they do on Mondays.
对哦 周一去面食工厂
Oh, right, yeah, yeah. Uh, P-Pasta Factory Monday.
我知道
I knew that.
看起来你不知道
Doesn't seem like you did.
休息时间结束了 去完成工作
Break time's over. Get your work done.
看来某人的愤怒"朋理"有些问题啊
Looks like someone has an issue with anger franagement.
开始扔吧
Let 'er rip!
真是一尊大炮
What a cannon!
-每小时58英里 -等等 什么
- 58 miles per hour. - Wait. What?!
是啊
Yes!
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
我们去超市时
When we were at the mall,
买了这个棒球 能显示扔得有多快
we got this baseball shows you how fast you throw it.
你们一起去逛了超市吗
You guys went to the mall together?
是啊
Yes, we sure did.
我们在西尔斯超市拿到了免费画像 以此证明
And we got the free portrait at Sears to prove it.
我们得扫描那幅画 免得它被毁了
We should scan that bad boy before it gets ruined.
再见
Um...bye?
你出局了
You're outta there!
夫人 给你
Milady, for you.
发型看起来不错啊
Looking good there, haircut!
他在这里啊 我的K歌小伙伴
Ah, there he is! There's my karaoke partner.
下次你唱埃博尼 我唱艾薇妮 好吗
Hey, listen, next time you're Ebony, I'm Ivory, all right?
工作了两天 还剩一天
Two days down, one to go,
办公室里的每个人依然爱这个全新的我
and everybody in the office still loves the new me.
咖啡过滤器脏了不要紧
Go ahead, leave a dirty coffee filter.
歪着停车吧
Oh, park askew.
随意的米奇尔不介意
Laid-back Mitchell doesn't mind.
当你所伪装的人
You know, it is really nice
受到大家的喜爱 这感觉真的很棒
to be liked for who you really are pretending to be.
好吧
All right.
今晚在罗娜的派对上见 好吗
I'm gonna see you tonight at Ronna's party, right?
好 什么派对
Okay. What party?
这问题真是英语中最可怜的四个字
Aw, the two saddest words in the English language.
没什么大不了的
Nah, it's no big deal.
我们只是在下班后去酒吧
We're just stopping by a bar after work,
喝点啤酒 吃点辣翅
have some beer, some hot wings.
-瞧瞧我 -不 没事
- Look at me. - No, it's cool.
这是我的错
This is my fault.
我刚来这里上班时
When I first started here,
有人邀请我参加活动 我拒绝了
somebody asked me to do something and I said no,
现在他们觉得我不感兴趣
and now they think I'm not interested.
可能是因为这个吧
Yeah, that's probably it.
但是我也许会去参加这次活动
I might drop by this one, though.
我觉得大家会高兴的
I think people would appreciate it.
你不能去
No, you can't go.
什么 为什么
What? Why not?
你知道你觉得
Well, you know how y-you think
你是他们的老板加朋友吧
that you're their boss and their friend?
你只是其中之一
You're one of those things.
天啊 他们讨厌我
Oh, my god. They hate me.
不 很多人喜欢你
No. Lots of people like you.
比如说谁
Like who?
我 我喜欢
Uh, well, me. I do.
-还有呢 -还有...
- Yeah? - And, um, the, uh...
爸爸 爸爸可喜欢你了
Dad. Dad's a big fan.
我的小天使怎么样
How's my little angel?
-今天不怎么样 -我在适应
- Not great today. - I'm settling in.
不是你俩 是斯黛拉
Not you two -- Stella.
她挺好
Oh, she's fine.
小卡在悉心地照顾她
Cam's taking great care of her.
有没有经常带她遛弯
Is she getting enough walks?
小卡中午回家吃午餐
Cam comes home from work at lunch,
带她去狗狗公园
takes her right to the dog park.
实际上 他现在就和她在狗狗公园
In fact, he's there with her right now.
不要去巴林顿的那个
Not the one on Barrington.
那里有只没阉过的松狮狗
'Cause there's an unsnipped chow
总是想搞她
always tries to hump her silly.
你好 普里契特先生
Oh, hi, Mr. Pritchett.
你好 露西
Hey, Lucy.
露西喜欢你
Lucy likes you.
克莱尔 看看我的新衬衫
Hey, Claire, check out my new shirt.
我要谢谢你
I have you to thank.
我可没功劳
Oh, no, that's all you.
你应该跟她谈谈的
You were supposed to talk to her
让她把那一对爆乳塞进衣服里
about storing those zeppelins in a hangar.
我说了
I did!
再说一遍 大声点 这里是办公场所
Well, do it again. Louder. This is a place of business.
她必须用布把她那俩球罩上
She needs to throw a tarp over those bounce houses.
爸爸 我觉得你才是无礼的那个人
Dad, I think you're the one who's being offensive.
这是我的公司 你搞定她
It's my company. Take care of it.
喂
Hello?
你在哪个狗公园
What dog park are you at?
你也下午好 杰
Good afternoon to you, too, Jay.
斯黛拉和我在牧场
Stella and I are at rancho.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
你要小心好色的松狮狗
Keep your eye out for Randy Chows.
那个花样溜冰运动员吗
The figure skater?
保证斯黛拉的安全就好了
Just keep Stella's safe.
杰 她很好 她玩得很开心
Jay, she's fine. She's having a great time.
等着 我给你发一张
H-here, I'm gonna send you
刚才我给她拍得滑稽照片
a hilarious picture I just took of her.
她从未这么开心过
She's never looked happier.
大概只是对你表示礼貌
Probably just being polite.
你给我看的是什么
What the hell am I looking at?
天呐 我给你发了什么
Oh, god, w-what -- what did I send you?
她脖子上是什么东西
What's that thing around her neck?
那就是条新项圈
Uh, that is just a new collar.
她以前的项圈太旧了
Her old one was looking a little tattered.
你不许给她买礼物
Don't go buying her presents!
她现在还是我的狗
She's still my dog.
你只是帮我看狗的人
You're a glorified kennel.
那只是我用珠宝装饰的一个小项圈
It's just a fun little collar that I bejeweled.
下一步是什么 你要给她穿上网袜
What's next? You gonna dress her in fishnets,
把她放到阿姆斯特丹的橱窗里吗
put her in a window in Amsterdam?
随意一点就好
Just keep it casual!
天呐 你真是个荡妇
Oh, my god. You're such a slut.
我爱死了
Oh, I love it.
没什么 我只是带我妹妹
Nothing, I'm just taking my sister
来咖啡店参加大学面试
to a college interview at a coffee shop.
我知道 不是吗
I know, right?
我差点忘了告诉你昨晚发生的事了
Oh, I totally forgot to tell you what happened last night.
丽莎 恩佐和我在回音公园的一个酒吧
Lisa, Enzo, and I were at a bar in Echo Park,
然后恩佐说
and Enzo was like,
"我的梦想就是在道奇体育场跑垒"
"My dream is to run the bases at Dodger Stadium."
于是我说"管他呢 我们这就去吧"
So I'm like, "Screw it, let's do it."
丽莎把头发卷到棒球帽里面
So, Lisa tucks her hair up to a baseball cap,
我们跟看场的人说她是贾斯汀·比伯
and we convince the grounds keeper that she's Justin Bieber
而那个贾斯汀会跟他合影
and that "Justin" will take a picture with him.
居然成功了
And it worked!
不 你闭嘴 这还不是最精彩的部分
No, you shut up! That's not even the best part.
恩佐开始跑垒
Enzo starts running the bases,
他把衣服脱下来扔了出去
and he whips his shirt off.
衣服被丽莎接到了 然后她也脱了衣服
And Lisa gets caught up in it and takes off her shirt,
然后看场人就说
And the grounds keeper's like,
"你不是贾斯汀·比伯"
"Whoa, you're not Justin Bieber."
然后他就开始拿着靶子追我们
So he starts chasing us around with a rake.
我知道
I know!
等等 那是谁
Oh, wait. Who is that?
丹尼丝吗 让那个婊子来接电话
Denise? Put that dirty hooker on the phone.
姐妹 我告诉你昨晚发生的事情了吗
Hey, girl. Did I tell you what happened last night?
恩佐说他的梦想就是
So, Enzo said that his dream
在道奇体育场跑垒
was to run the bases at Dodger Stadium,
-我说"管他呢 我们这就去吧" -老天呐
- and I was like, "Screw it, let's do it." - Oh, my god!
你的嘴就不能歇一会儿吗
Do you ever stop talking?!
我坐在这里试图在精神上
I am sitting here trying to mentally prepare
为我一生中最重要的时刻做准备
for one of the most important moments of my life,
能不能麻烦你把嘴闭上
so can you please just shut up?
我知道 不是吗
I know, right? Ohh.
好了 看起来他们要结束了
All right, looks like they're finishing up.
我现在应该进去了
I should probably go in now.
告诉她裙子很可爱 公主娜娜的秋装
Ooh, tell her cute dress -- Nanette Lepore, fall collection.
好极了 我就用"可爱的裙子"开场
Great. I'll open with, "Cute dress."
可爱的裙子
Cute dress.
安迪 离开放日还有36小时
Andy, 36 hours to the open house.
准备好了吗
You ready?
我生来就准备好了
I was born ready.
事实上 那是假的
Actually, that's not true.
我早产了两个月
I was two months premature,
生下来才三斤重
weighed three and a half pounds.
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous.
只有一个方法来解决...
There's only one way to get over that --
模拟开放日
Mock open house!
倒数计时 五 四...
Starting in five...four...
忘了拿名片
Uh, business card!
你不是安迪
You're not Andy.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint you.
我在这
I'm here!
欢迎 快进来
Welcome. Come on in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
在干什么
What's happening?
我要带邓菲先生
I was about to give Mr. Dunphy here
参观这所漂亮的大房子
a tour of this beautiful open house.
我不认识邓菲先生 虽然听起来他很酷
I do not know who Mr. Dunphy is, although he sounds cool.
我只是从图森搬来的帅气的整形医生
I'm just a handsome plastic surgeon relocating from Tucson.
我是他的儿子
And I'm his son.
好主意 假装是我的儿子
Good idea. Pretend to be my son.
这就是厨房吗
So, is this the kitchen?
问得好 这就是厨房
Great question. Yes, it is.
完全更新成为开放式厨房
Fully updated with an open floor plan,
大家庭的完美选择
perfect for large families.
你和你的夫人还有别的孩子吗
Do you and the missus have other kids?
没有 就我一个 所以这有点太大了
Nope, just me, so it's way too big.
你看起来工作能力很差
You seem terrible at your job.
我不知道
I don't know.
你们看起来像是拥有很多朋友的家庭
You seem like a family with a lot of friends.
招待客人的话会很方便
It's great for entertaining.
这里的邻居多元化情况怎么样
How diverse is the neighborhood?
我这样问是因为
I only ask because I'm married
我娶了一位非洲裔的美人
to a beautiful African-American woman.
不能告诉你她是谁
I can't say who,
不过你在《阿凡达》里见过她
but you may know her from "Avatar."
住在这一带的人
This neighborhood has a wonderful mix
来自不同的民族和种族
of different cultures and ethnicities.
-听起来很危险 -卢克
- Ooh, sounds dangerous. - Luke...
你们要知道的就是
Here's all you need to know --
在过去的两年里 这附近的房产价值
In the last two years, home values in this neighborhood
已经比城市平均值高了两倍
have increased by twice the city average.
这里很安静 也很安全
It's quiet. It's safe.
我想不到有什么地方比这里
I can't think of a better place
更适合建立一个美丽的混血家庭
to raise a beautiful mixed-race family.
我要跟佐伊简单谈一下
I'm gonna have to have a quick conversation with Zoe,
不过我想你已经卖出了这套房子
but I think you just sold a house.
太好了
Yes!
太好了 终于完了
Good. Is this finally done?
爸爸 我想你和我是不是该
'Cause, dad, I was thinking maybe you and I
穿上燕尾服去劳斯莱斯试驾
could put on tuxedos and test-drive Rolls-Royces.
卢克 对不起 真希望我能去
Aw, Luke, I'm sorry. I wish I could,
不过我已经答应安迪教他怎么系领带了
but I already promised Andy I'd teach him how to tie a tie.
来吧伙计 我有首系领带的小曲子教给你
Come on, buddy. I got a song and everything.
我必须要告诉你
I have to let you know,
我的脖子特别怕痒
my neck is extraordinarily ticklish.
是真的吗
You don't say.
你敢
Don't you dare.
不要 不要
Don't. Don't!
-快过来 -不 不要
- Get over here! - No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
很高兴见到你 吉塔
It was so nice to meet you, Gita.
我会发给你我的大管独奏录音的
I'll be sure to send you that recording of my bassoon solo.
最好是
You'd better!
你能隔着电话杀了我吗
Could you kill me over the phone?
天呐 这些孩子全都一样
Oh, my God. These kids are all the same.
请告诉我
Please tell me
我们申请的时候没有这么无聊到爆
we weren't this aggressively boring when we applied.
都是辩论队 管弦乐队 预科 高绩点
It's all debate team, orchestra, A.P., GPA.
我真想一巴掌糊上她洋洋自得的脸
I wanted to smack one of them in her smug little face,
不过我觉得她就是个机器人
But I'm pretty sure she was a robot.
我真想见几个不这么无聊的人
I can't believe I'm missing spinning for this.
你好 我是艾丽克斯·邓菲
Hi. I'm Alex Dunphy.
我得挂了
I got to go.
太好了 请坐 我是瓦内萨
Oh, great. Have a seat. I'm Vanessa.
想来点咖啡吗
Would you like some coffee?
不 谢谢 但关于咖啡有这么个故事
No, thanks, but I actually have a crazy fact about coffee --
蜜蜂喜欢咖啡因 因为花蜜里也有
bees love caffeine because it's found in nectar,
不过我对B的了解没那么多
but I don't know that much about B's,
我的成绩单上大多是A
as you can see from my transcript.
你资料上说你是辩论队的
So, I see here that you're on the debate team
你还拉大提琴
and you play the cello.
是的 不过我的生活远不止这些
Yes, but I am so much more than that.
我还是法语俱乐部的
I'm also a part of the French club.
跟我说说
Tell me more.
很抱歉浪费了你的时间
I'm so sorry for wasting your time.
我犯了个大错
This was a big mistake.
我也许不是上普林斯顿的料
I'm probably not Princeton material anyways.
我昨晚大部分时间
I mean, I spent most of last night
都待在一部警察巡逻车后座
in the back of a squad car.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
疯狂的故事
Well, crazy story --
我朋友恩佐的梦想
My friend Enzo's dream
是在道奇体育场上跑垒
was to run the bases at Dodger stadium.
我说 "管他呢 我们这就去吧"
And I was just like, "Screw it, let's do it."
顺便说一句 裙子很好看
Oh, by the way, cute dress.
是"公主娜娜"的吗
Is that a Nanette Lepore?
是的 眼光不错
Oh, my God, yes. Good eye.
然后呢
So, what happened next?
然后我朋友丽莎
Well, then my friend Lisa
把头发塞进棒球帽
tucks her hair up into a baseball cap,
跟看场的人说她是贾斯汀·比伯
and we convince the grounds keeper that she's Justin Bieber
而这个贾斯汀愿意跟他合个影
and that "Justin" will take a picture with him.
天呐
Oh, my God.
你真淘气 我喜欢
You're so naughty. I love it.
你知道的 贱人
You know it, slut.
天呐 真抱歉
Oh, my God. I am so sorry.
晚餐你给我们做牛排吗 太棒了
Aww, you're cooking us a steak dinner -- how sweet.
是啊 我提前下班回来做我们的晚餐
Yeah, I came home from work early to cook us dinner.
你疯了吗
That's crazy.
这是给斯黛拉的
This is for Stella.
杰
Ay, Jay...
你不知道我面临多强的竞争对手
You don't know what I'm competing with over there.
卡梅隆帮她按摩肚皮
Cameron's wooing her with belly rubs,
买珠宝 亲嘴嘴
jewelry, kisses on the mouth.
我就想让她记得谁最爱她
I just want her to remember who loves her the most.
我不觉得斯黛拉会忘记
I don't think Stella is ever going to forget
你有多爱她
how much you love her,
不管她跟米奇和小卡
No matter how much time
还要一同度过多少时间
she needs to stay with Mitch and Cam.
你在说什么 她周五就回来
What are you talking about? She's coming home Friday.
是这样的
That's the thing.
看
Look.
疹子没了
The rash is gone.
我们不能确定是不是因为斯黛拉
Well, we don't know that's Stella.
很多原因都会造成疹子
A lot of things cause rashes.
说不定他只是没有上周那么大压力了
Maybe he's less stressed this week than last.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
我们得送走斯黛拉
We have to get rid of Stella.
等等 我们还没作出决定呢
Slow down. We haven't decided anything yet.
我们决定好了 这是对乔最好的
Yes, we have. It's what's best for Joe.
而且值得一提 我的眼睛也不痒了
And for whatever it's worth, my eyes have stopped itching,
我能尝出食物的味儿 也更有精神了
I can taste my food, and I have more energy.
你昨天打了三个小时的盹
You took a three-hour nap yesterday.
我跑完马拉松太累了
I was tired from the marathon.
看《唐顿庄园》马拉松吗
The "Downton Abbey" Marathon?
那个家族太累人了
That family is exhausting.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
杰 抱歉
Ah, Jay, I'm so sorry.
要不你养条鱼吧
Maybe you can get a fish!
当然 因为开车时让你的宠物鱼
'cause it's so much cuter driving down the road
把头潇洒地伸出窗外要"酷"多了
with your fish's head sticking out the window.
鱼
Fish!
天呐
Oh, my God.
你要来再给我上一课吗
Are you here for another lecture?
你已经讲得够明白了
Because you made your point loud and clear.
我已经很随意了
I'm keeping it casual.
我今早都没正眼看过斯黛拉
I haven't even looked at Stella this morning.
好吧 别想太多
Okay, do not read too much into that --
那是我从莉莉的泰迪熊身上脱下来的
I just took that off one of Lily's Teddy Bears.
没事
It's fine.
你们宠她我挺高兴的
I'm glad you guys are spoiling her,
因为我已经没法宠她了
because I won't be able to anymore.
乔对她过敏
Joe's allergic.
不是吧
No.
而且既然她这么喜欢你们
Yeah, and I figured since she likes you so much,
你们可以一直养着她
maybe you guys could keep her.
如果这样对所有人都好的话
Well, I mean, if that's what's best for everyone.
你要不要先跟米奇商量一下
Maybe you better check with Mitch first?
他会同意的
He'll deal.
我给她做了块牛排
I made her a steak.
好吧
Okay.
这是她的沙发床
And this is her daybed.
我也许该道个别了
I guess I better say goodbye.
亲爱的
Hi, sweetie.
过来 我想跟你聊一下
Come here. I want to talk to you.
好了 宝贝
Now, honey,
你以后就要住在这里了
you're gonna live here from now on.
别这么看着我
Don't give me that look.
你什么都没做错
It wasn't anything you did.
你是世界上最好的狗狗
You've been the best dog I could ever have asked for,
我非常爱你 所以
and I love you very much. So...
注意避开车子
stay away from cars...
不要吃锋利的东西
Don't eat anything pointy...
做个乖女孩
and be a good girl.
再见 斯黛拉宝贝
Goodbye, Stella-bella.
不敢相信我居然没哭出来
I didn't think I'd get through that without crying.
我也是
Me neither.
老爸 来看这个视频
Hey, dad, check out this video.
一头茶杯猪在弹钢琴
It's a teacup pig playing a piano.
我看过了 安迪给我发的
I saw that. Andy sent it to me.
不可思议
Unbelievable.
我开始也这么想
That's what I thought,
不过我们后来做了调查
but then Andy and I did some digging.
原来猪超有音乐天赋
It turns out pigs are crazy musical.
又是安迪
Good ol' Andy.
有什么问题吗
Is something up, buddy?
我就拒绝了你一次
I said "no" one time.
结果现在你说的都是安迪怎么怎么样
And suddenly it's all "Andy this" and "Andy that."
我没别的意思
Well, I didn't mean anything by it.
你看上去需要一点个人空间
It just seemed like you needed some space,
所以我给你空间
so I gave it to you.
我懂的
I get it.
你到了想独立自主的年纪
You're at that age when you want to separate.
是我从你那独立出来
Yeah, I separate from you,
而不是反过来
not the other way around.
也许我不想老跟着你做一些傻事
Maybe I don't want to do dumb stuff with you all the time,
可是
but
这不代表你能找人取代我
that doesn't mean you get to replace me.
什么
What?
你开玩笑吗 我永远不可能找人取代你
Are you kidding me? I could never replace you.
如果我来决定 我们会一起做所有的事
If it were up to me, we'd do everything together.
真的吗
Really?
我会跟你一起读大学
Yeah, I'd go to college with you.
我们可以当室友 一起进兄弟会
We’d-we'd be roommates. We'd try to join a frat.
没有一个兄弟会愿意要我们
None of them would take us.
我们自己办一个
We'd start our own.
天呐 听起来太棒了
Oh, my God. That sounds amazing.
为什么没人要我们
Why wouldn't they take us?
他们肯定会要我 但我会说
Well, yeah, they'd take me, but I'd be like,
想都别想 布拉德利
"No way, Bradley,
没有我的小伙伴我是不会来的
not without my little pal, here."
关于这个 我心情有点复杂
I have mixed feelings about that, dad.
你对一个拥抱也会心情复杂吗
Do you have mixed feelings about a hug?
会
Yes.
我需要个拥抱 那我去拥抱安迪了
Well, I need one, so I guess I'm gonna go hug Andy.
好吧
Fine.
朱迪 那封邮件太好笑了
Hey, Judy, that was a hilarious e-mail.
酸黄瓜比男人更好用
Pickles are better than men.
你懂吗 太好笑了
Did you get that? It was so--
你来这之后有干活吗
Have you done any work since you came here?
我在调动工作气氛
I'm working the room.
看 运动装帅哥
There he is. Sport coat.
运动装
Sport coat?
真不敢相信 这些白痴居然觉得你幽默
I can't believe these idiots think you're funny.
说起来 我有个理论
Okay. You know, I have a theory
是关于为何这里的人不喜欢你
why people here don't like you.
我知道他们为何不喜欢我
I know why they don't like me.
因为老爸把得罪人的活都扔给我了
It's cause dad makes me do all his dirty work.
看看我今天要训斥多少人
Look at this list of people I'm supposed to reprimand today.
来看看
Let's see here.
他确实是对的 格伦有体臭
Well, he does have a point, Glen does smell.
我要先从露西开始
I'm gonna start with Lucy.
露西 唯一喜欢我的人
Lucy, the last person who likes me.
没关系的
Oh, it's okay.
露西
Hey, Luce.
克莱尔 我给你留了你喜欢的饼干
Hey, Claire. I got you one of those cookies that you like.
别让我更加不忍心开口
Oh, don't make this harder than it has to be.
-出什么事了吗 -的确有事
- Is there something wrong? - Yes.
开口说这个很难 不过
It's not easy for me to discuss, but--
克莱尔 我来吧
Claire, I got this.
毕竟是我的投诉 我来
It's my complaint. I got it.
露西
Lucy...
你是在上班 所以请穿得像上班
you're at work, so please dress like it.
你穿的这些上衣完全不得体
These "Tops" that you wear are completely inappropriate.
抱歉冒犯到你了
Sorry to offend you.
你知道吗
You know what?
反正都要说的 格伦 你得勤洗澡
While I'm at it, Glen, shower more often.
查克 别再随便用"回复给所有人"
Chuck, stop using "Reply all."
还有多莉丝 没人在乎
A-and, Doris, no one cares
你昨晚都梦到了什么
about what you dreamt about last night.
大家都记住了 这里是工作场所
Let's keep in mind this is a place of business, folks,
明白了吗
all right?
感觉真好
This feels good.
有没有人叫卡尔
Is there a Carl?!
律师啊
Lawyers.
我说得没错吧 运动装
Am I right, sport coat?
那不是他
That's not sport coat.
我回家了
I'm home.
你感觉怎么样
Oh, hi. How are you feeling?
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
杰 我真为你骄傲
Oh, Jay, I'm so proud of you.
今天你做出了牺牲
You made a sacrifice today.
为了自己的儿子 你做了正确的选择
You did the right thing for your son.
看他有多开心
Look how happy he is.
可能吧
I guess.
等等
Wait a minute.
-他脖子上是什么 -什么
- What's that on his neck? - What?
他的皮疹又复发了
His rash came back.
不
No.
你的手肯定沾到了斯黛拉的狗毛
You must have some Stella on you.
不 我之后直接去了俱乐部
No, no, I went to straight to the club after.
在那洗了个澡 哭了一下
Took a shower, maybe cried a little bit in there,
重新换了衣服
changed clothes to make sure.
何况我才刚回来呢
Plus, I just got here.
皮疹长出来的时间比这长
A rash would take longer to come out.
那是什么味道
What's that smell?
-什么味道 -闻起来像花
- What smell? - It smells like flowers or something.
我可没买花
I didn't get any flowers.
我闻到味道了 歌洛莉亚
I smell something, Gloria.
家里有什么东西不一样
What's new around here?
不一样的就是你觉得有东西不一样
The fact that you noticed something.
就是你
It's you.
什么是新的 是什么呢
What's new? What?
香水 还是唇膏
Perfume, lipstick?
我闻到了薰衣草 还有
I'm getting lavender with,
还有玫瑰果
I want to say rose hips.
是你的面霜
It's your face cream!
我今早是买了几瓶 不过
I did buy some more this morning, but--
你买的是乔的皮疹消褪前
The same kind that Stella was eating
斯黛拉吃的那种面霜吗
before Joe's rash cleared up?
现在你抹回了面霜 他的皮疹又回来了
And now you're wearing it again, and his rash is back?
不可能是我的面霜
No, it can't be my face cream!
不要让我跟心爱的面霜告别
Please don't make me say goodbye to my face cream!
斯黛拉吃面霜是为了救乔
Stella was eating it to save Joe!
但这还是不能解释
But that still doesn't explain
为什么我感觉好多了
why I'm still feeling so much better.
我可以呼吸
I can breathe for th--
斯黛拉要作为"狗雄"回家啦
Stella's coming home a hero!
莉莉 你能出来一下吗
Lily, can you come out here, please?
为什么要这么做
Why do we have to do this?
因为她们产生了感情 杰
Because she's become attached, Jay.
她们现在都要一起睡觉
She's even sleeping with her now.
外公
Hi, grandpa.
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
莉莉 你记得我说过
Lily, do you remember how I said
斯黛拉从今以后要和我们住在一起吗
Stella was gonna be staying with us from now on?
事实上
Well, it turns out...
她要和外公一起回去了
she's gonna go home with grandpa.
好吧
Okay.
莉莉 表达自己的感受很重要
Lily, it's important to express your feelings.
不要把它们藏在心里
Don't bottle them up.
我睡觉终于不用听她打呼了
Okay. I can finally sleep without all of her snoring!
够了 把她给我
All right, enough. Hand her over.
到这来 宝贝
Come here, baby.
那是什么
What is that?
别笑我 我现在很脆弱
Please don't make fun of me. I'm very vulnerable right now.
你能帮我弄一件吗
Can you get me one?